http://www.firstmagazine.com/privacy.aspx

skip navigation
HomeAbout UsProfileManagementSenior AdvisorsTestimonialsRecruitmentContact UsPublishingAbout PublishingFIRST MagazineSpecial ReportsSpecialist PublishingBooksEventsAbout Events2020 Events2019 Events2018 EventsArchiveAwardsAbout AwardsAward Advisory Panel2019 Award2018 Award2017 Award2016 Award2015 AwardArchiveMake a NominationNewsPartnersReadership/AdvertisingReadership ProfileAdvertisingEditorial Style SheetMechanical DataSubscribe/Purchase
Home
Home
FIRST Magazine Limited - Privacy Policy
FIRST Magazine Limited is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Because we operate from
offices in more than one country, we have taken steps to ensure that high
standards of data protection are adhered to globally for all the forms of data
processing mentioned below. This statement outlines our privacy and data
protection policy.
Collection and use of customer information
Your personal details will be collected and processed when you order, purchase,
register, subscribe or make use of any of our products or services. Information
is collected by the companies of FIRST Magazine Limited. FIRST Magazine Limited
is registered with the United Kingdom's Information Commissioner's Office as a data
controller in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
When you visit any of our websites, we also collect website usage information,
and information about your computer and internet connection. This includes your
computer's IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you
use, your internet domain and, if you visited via a link from another website,
the URL of the linking page.
This information is collected to help us:
fulfil your order
manage your registration preferences
send you renewal notifications
personalise web content and advertising based on your personal
characteristics or preferences
ensure, as far as is practical, that our websites are compatible
with the browsers and operating systems used by most of our visitors
conduct customer satisfaction surveys
We also use your information for in-house research and
analysis. This helps us to:
improve our understanding of customer needs
create marketing profiles
support strategic development
To enable us to conduct research we may share your information
with third party suppliers employed to help. All results of any research
and analysis will be information that is aggregated or rendered anonymous
and will not reveal any personal details of individual customers.
You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold. Email your request to our data protection officer Christopher Cammack
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which is
placed on your hard drive when you visit the FIRST Magazine website. We use
information from cookies for purposes which may include:
identifying returning users, registrants and subscribers
eliminating the need for returning users to re-enter their login
details
enabling you to move more easily around our site
tracking your use of our site to better develop our site in
accordance with your requirements
building up an anonymous profile based on your browsing patterns
across our site and third party websites, which enables us to make content
available to you that is more relevant to your interests
You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any
time. Bear in mind, though, that if you delete them, any settings such as your
stored username and password will have to be reset when you next log in.
You will be able to use our website even if your
browser is not set to accept cookies. However, certain features and content may
not be available to you and you will have to log in every time you visit.
If you specifically do not wish us to collect cookie
information for the purpose of content and behavioural targeted advertising,
you can "opt out" by following the instructions at http://www.cookiecentral.com.
Further information on the use of cookies can be found
at: www.cookiecentral.com/faq.
External links
Our website may contain links to
external sites. FIRST Magazine Limited is not responsible for the privacy
policies or the content of such sites and we recommend that you read the
privacy policies on any external sites you use.
Security policy
FIRST Magazine Limited does its utmost
to protect your privacy and ensure your personal details are not misused,
accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within FIRST Magazine Limited.
Occasionally we share your details with other
companies who are managing data for us (e.g. fulfilment bureaux, database
consultants etc.). They are only permitted to process your data with explicit
permission from FIRST Magazine Limited, enabling them to perform the services
required.
Children under 13
FIRST Magazine Limited does not intentionally collect any personal information
from individuals under the age of 13. When necessary, underage users will be
told not to submit any personal details and we will make every effort to delete
any details of such users where a parent or guardian has informed us that these
details have been collected.
Changes to this statement
From time to time, we may make changes to the privacy policy. This may be in
relation to changes in the law, best practice or changes in our services. These
changes will be reflected in this statement, so you should check here from time
to time.
Last amended: May 2018
Back to top
All content © Copyright 2020 First | Site Design by Trickster
6 Vigo Street, Mayfair, London W1S 3HF, UK
|
Terms & Conditions | Privacy PolicyTel: +44 (0) 20 7440 3500
|
Company No: 02017939
